shoponn.in 2019-07-23

# Privacy Policy - shoponn.in

###  Privacy Policy

* * *

We value the trust you place in us. That's why we insist upon the highest standards for secure transactions and customer information privacy. Please read the following statement to learn about our information gathering and dissemination practices. 

**Note:** Our privacy policy is subject to change at any time without notice. To make sure you are aware of any changes, please review this policy periodically. By visiting this Website you agree to be bound by the terms and conditions of this Privacy Policy. If you do not agree please do not use or access our Website. By mere use of the Website, you expressly consent to our use and disclosure of your personal information in accordance with this Privacy Policy. This Privacy Policy is incorporated into and subject to the Terms of Use. 

THIS PRIVACY POLICY IS AN ELECTRONIC RECORD IN THE FORM OF AN ELECTRONIC CONTRACT FORMED UNDER THE INFORMATION TECHNOLOGY ACT, 2000 AND THE RULES MADE THEREUNDER AND THE AMENDED PROVISIONS PERTAINING TO ELECTRONIC DOCUMENTS / RECORDS IN VARIOUS STATUTES AS AMENDED BY THE INFORMATION TECHNOLOGY ACT, 2000. THIS PRIVACY POLICY DOES NOT REQUIRE ANY PHYSICAL, ELECTRONIC OR DIGITAL SIGNATURE. 

If you incur return shipping charges over Rs.60 for returning large and heavy items, you can contact us for an additional refund. 

THIS PRIVACY POLICY IS A LEGALLY BINDING DOCUMENT BETWEEN YOU AND shoponn (BOTH TERMS DEFINED BELOW). THE TERMS OF THIS PRIVACY POLICY WILL BE EFFECTIVE UPON YOUR ACCEPTANCE OF THE SAME (DIRECTLY OR INDIRECTLY IN ELECTRONIC FORM, BY CLICKING ON THE I ACCEPT TAB OR BY USE OR THE WEBSITE OR BY OTHER MEANS) AND WILL GOVERN THE RELATIONSHIP BETWEEN YOU AND shoponn FOR YOUR USE OF THE WEBSITE (DEFINED BELOW). 

THIS DOCUMENT IS PUBLISHED AND SHALL BE CONSTRUED IN ACCORDANCE WITH THE PROVISIONS OF THE INFORMATION TECHNOLOGY (REASONABLE SECURITY PRACTICES AND PROCEDURES AND SENSITIVE PERSONAL DATA OF INFORMATION) RULES, 2011 UNDER INFORMATION TECHNOLOGY ACT, 2000; THAT REQUIRE PUBLISHING OF THE PRIVACY POLICY FOR COLLECTION, USE, STORAGE AND TRANSFER OF SENSITIVE PERSONAL DATA OR INFORMATION. 

PLEASE READ THIS PRIVACY POLICY CAREFULLY. BY USING THE WEBSITE, YOU INDICATE THAT YOU UNDERSTAND, AGREE AND CONSENT TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY. IF YOU DO NOT AGREE WITH THE TERMS OF THIS PRIVACY POLICY, PLEASE DO NOT USE THIS WEBSITE. YOU HEREBY PROVIDE YOUR UNCONDITIONAL CONSENT OR AGREEMENTS TO shoponn AS PROVIDED UNDER SECTION 43A AND SECTION 72A OF INFORMATION TECHNOLOGY ACT, 2000. 

By providing us your Information or by making use of the facilities provided by the Website, you hereby consent to the collection, storage, processing and transfer of any or all of your Personal Information and Non-Personal Information by shoponn as specified under this Privacy Policy. You further agree that such collection, use, storage and transfer of your Information shall not cause any loss or wrongful gain to you or any other person. 

Nipurn Engineering Private Limited and its subsidiaries and affiliates and Associate Companies (individually and/ or collectively, "shoponn") is/are concerned about the privacy of the data and information of users (including sellers and buyers/customers whether registered or non- registered) accessing, offering, selling or purchasing products or services on shoponn’s websites, mobile sites or mobile applications ("Website") on the Website and otherwise doing business with shoponn. Associate Companies here shall have the same meaning as in Companies Act, 2013. 

The terms We /Us/Our individually and collectively refer to each entity being part of the definition of shoponn and the terms "You" / "Your" / "Yourself refer to the users. This Privacy Policy is a contract between you and the respective shoponn entity whose Website you use or access or you otherwise deal with. This Privacy Policy shall be read together with the respective Terms of Use or other terms and condition of the respective shoponn entity and its respective Website or nature of business of the Website. 

####  shoponn has provided this Privacy Policy to familiarize you with. 

  * The type of data or information that You share with or provide to shoponn and that shoponn collects from You; 
  * The purpose for collection of such data or information from You; shoponn’s information security practices and policies; and 
  * shoponn’s policy on sharing or transferring, your data or information with third parties. 

This Privacy Policy may be amended / updated from time to time. Upon amending / updating the Privacy Policy, we will accordingly amend the date above. We suggest that you regularly check this Privacy Policy to apprise yourself of any updates. Your continued use of Website or provision of data or information thereafter will imply your unconditional acceptance of such updates to this Privacy Policy. 

####  A. Purpose for collecting, using, storing, and processing your information

shoponn collects, uses, stores and processes Your Information for any purpose as may be permissible under applicable laws (including where the applicable law provides for such collection, usage, storage or processes in accordance with the consent of the user) connected with a function or activity of each of shoponn entities and shall include the following: 

  * to facilitate Your use of the Website or other services of shoponn entities; 
  * to respond to Your inquiries or fulfil Your requests for information about the various products and services offered on the Website; 
  * to provide You with information about products and services available on the Website and to send You information, materials, and offers from shoponn; 
  * to send You important information regarding the Website, changes in terms and conditions, user agreements, and policies and/or other administrative information; 
  * to send you surveys and marketing communications that shoponn believes may be of interest to You; 
  * to personalize your experience on the Website by presenting advertisements, products and offers tailored to Your preferences; 
  * to help you address your problems incurred on the Website including addressing any technical problems; 
  * if you purchase any product or avail of any service from the Website, to complete and fulfill your purchase, for example, to have Your payments processed, communicate with you regarding Your purchase and provide You with related customer service; 
  * for proper administering of the Website; 
  * to conduct internal reviews and data analysis for the Website (e.g., to determine the number of visitors to specific pages within the Website); 
  * to improve the services, content and advertising on the Website; 
  * to provide value added services such as Single Sign On. Single Sign On shall mean a session/user authentication process that permits a user to enter his/her name or mobile number or e-mail address or any combination thereof and password in order to access multiple websites and applications; 
  * to facilitate various programmes and initiatives launched by shoponn or third party service providers and business associates 
  * to analyze how our services are used, to measure the effectiveness of advertisements, to facilitating payments 
  * to conducting academic research and surveys 
  * to protect the integrity of the Website; 
  * to respond to legal, judicial, quasi judicial process and provide information to law enforcement agencies or in connection with an investigation on matters related to public safety, as permitted by law; 
  * to conduct analytical studies on various aspects including user behaviour, user preferences etc.; 
  * to permit third parties who may need to contact users who have bought products from the Website to facilitate installation, service and any other product related support; 
  * to implement information security practices; 
  * to determine any security breaches, computer contaminant or computer virus; 
  * to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities and suspected fraud, 
  * to undertake forensics of the concerned computer resource as a part of investigation or internal audit; 
  * to trace computer resources or any person who may have contravened, or is suspected of having or being likely to contravene, any provision of law including the Information Technology Act, 2000 that is likely to have an adverse impact on the services provided on any Website or by shoponn; 
  * to enable a potential buyer or investor to evaluate the business of shoponn(as further described in the Privacy Policy). 

You hereby agree and acknowledge that the Information so collected is for lawful purpose connected with a function or activity of each of the shoponn entities or any person on their respective behalf, and the collection of Information is necessary for the Purposes. 

####  B. Collection of Personally Identifiable Information and other Information

When you use our Website, we collect and store your personal information which is provided by you from time to time. Our primary goal in doing so is to provide you a safe, efficient, smooth and customized experience. This allows us to provide services and features that most likely meet your needs, and to customize our Website to make your experience safer and easier. More importantly, while doing so we collect personal information from you that we consider necessary for achieving this purpose. 

In general, you can browse the Website without telling us who you are or revealing any personal information about yourself. Once you give us your personal information, you are not anonymous to us. Where possible, we indicate which fields are required and which fields are optional. You always have the option to not provide information by choosing not to use a particular service or feature on the Website. We may automatically track certain information about you based upon your behaviour on our Website. We use this information to do internal research on our users' demographics, interests, and behaviour to better understand, protect and serve our users. This information is compiled and analyzed on an aggregated basis. This information may include the URL that you just came from (whether this URL is on our Website or not), which URL you next go to (whether this URL is on our Website or not), your computer browser information, and your IP address. 

We use data collection devices such as "cookies" on certain pages of the Website to help analyse our web page flow, measure promotional effectiveness, and promote trust and safety. "Cookies" are small files placed on your hard drive that assist us in providing our services. We offer certain features that are only available through the use of a "cookie". We also use cookies to allow you to enter your password less frequently during a session. Cookies can also help us provide information that is targeted to your interests. Most cookies are "session cookies," meaning that they are automatically deleted from your hard drive at the end of a session. You are always free to decline our cookies if your browser permits, although in that case you may not be able to use certain features on the Website and you may be required to re-enter your password more frequently during a session. 

Additionally, you may encounter "cookies" or other similar devices on certain pages of the Website that are placed by third parties. We do not control the use of cookies by third parties. 

If you choose to buy on the Website, we collect information about your buying behaviour. 

If you transact with us, we collect some additional information, such as a billing address, a credit / debit card number and a credit / debit card expiration date and/ or other payment instrument details and tracking information from cheques or money orders. 

If you choose to post messages on our message boards, chat rooms or other message areas or leave feedback, we will collect that information you provide to us. We retain this information as necessary to resolve disputes, provide customer support and troubleshoot problems as permitted by law. 

If you send us personal correspondence, such as emails or letters, or if other users or third parties send us correspondence about your activities or postings on the Website, we may collect such information into a file specific to you. 

We collect personally identifiable information (email address, name, phone number, credit card / debit card / other payment instrument details, etc.) from you when you set up a free account with us. While you can browse some sections of our Website without being a registered member, certain activities (such as placing an order) do require registration. We do use your contact information to send you offers based on your previous orders and your interests. 

####  C.Use of Demographic / Profile Data / Your Information

We use personal information to provide the services you request. To the extent we use your personal information to market to you, we will provide you the ability to opt-out of such uses. We use your personal information to resolve disputes; troubleshoot problems; help promote a safe service; collect money; measure consumer interest in our products and services, inform you about online and offline offers, products, services, and updates; customize your experience; detect and protect us against error, fraud and other criminal activity; enforce our terms and conditions; and as otherwise described to you at the time of collection.

In our efforts to continually improve our product and service offerings, we collect and analyse demographic and profile data about our users' activity on our Website. We identify and use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server, and to administer our Website. Your IP address is also used to help identify you and to gather broad demographic information. 

We will occasionally ask you to complete optional online surveys. These surveys may ask you for contact information and demographic information (like zip code, age, or income level). We use this data to tailor your experience at our Website, providing you with content that we think you might be interested in and to display content according to your preferences. 

####  Cookies

A "cookie" is a small piece of information stored by a web server on a web browser so it can be later read back from that browser. Cookies are useful for enabling the browser to remember information specific to a given user. We place both permanent and temporary cookies in your computer's hard drive. The cookies do not contain any of your personally identifiable information.

####  D. Information collected and Storage

The Information (which shall also include data) provided by you to shoponn or collected from you by shoponn may consist of Personal Information and Non-Personal Information.

####  Personal Information

Personal Information is Information collected that can be used to uniquely identify or contact you. Personal Information for the purposes of this Privacy Policy shall include, but not be limited to: 

  * Your Name, Company Name
  * Your address,
  * Your telephone number, mobile number
  * Your e-mail address, website if any or other contact information,
  * Your date of birth,
  * Your gender,
  * Information regarding your transactions on the Website, (including sales or purchase history),
  * Your financial information such as bank account information or credit card or debit card or other payment instrument details,
  * Your financial information such as bank account information or credit card or debit card or other payment instrument details,
  * Internet Protocol address,
  * Any other items of sensitive personal data or information as such term is defined under the Information Technology (Reasonable Security Practices And Procedures And Sensitive Personal Data Of Information) Rules, 2011 enacted under the Information Technology Act, 2000;
  * Identification code of your communication device which you use to access the Website or otherwise deal with any shoponn entity,
  * Any other Information that you provide during your registration process, if any, on the Website.

####  Such Personal Information may be collected in various ways including during the course of You:

  * Registering as a user on the Website,
  * Registering as a seller on the Website,
  * Availing certain services offered on the Website. Such instances include but are not limited to making an offer for sale, online purchase, participating in any online survey or contest, communicating with shoponn’s customer service by phone, email or otherwise or posting user reviews on the items available on the Website, or
  * otherwise doing business on the Website or otherwise dealing with any shoponn entity.

We may receive Personal information about you from third parties, such as social media services, commercially available sources and business partners. If you access Website through a social media service or connect a service on Website to a social media service, the information we collect may include your user name associated with that social media service, any information or content the social media service has the right to share with us, such as your profile picture, email address or friends list, and any information you have made public in connection with that social media service. When you access the Website or otherwise deal with any shoponn entity through social media services or when you connect any Website to social media services, you are authorizing shoponn to collect, store, and use and retain such information and content in accordance with this Privacy Policy.

####  Non-Personal Information

shoponn may also collect information other than Personal Information from you through the Website when you visit and / or use the Website. Such information may be stored in server logs. This Non-Personal Information would not assist shoponn to identify you personally.

####  This Non-Personal Information may include:

  * Your geographic location, 
  * details of Your telecom service provider or internet service provider,
  * the type of browser (Internet Explorer, Firefox, Opera, Google Chrome etc.),
  * the operating system of your system, device and the Website You last visited before visiting the Website,
  * The duration of your stay on the Website is also stored in the session along with the date and time of your access,

Non-Personal Information is collected through various ways such through the use of cookies. shoponn may store temporary or permanent cookies on Your computer. You can erase or choose to block these cookies from your computer. You can configure Yourcomputer"s browser to alert you when we attempt to send you a cookie with an option to accept or refuse the cookie. If you have turned cookies off, you may be prevented from using certain features of the Website. 

Ads: shoponn may use third-party service providers to serve ads on shoponn’s behalf across the internet and sometimes on the Website. They may collect Non- Personal Information about Your visits to the Website, and Your interaction with our products and services on the Website. 

Please do note that Personal Information and Non Personal Information may be treated differently as per this Privacy Policy. 

####  You hereby represent to shoponn that 

  * the Information you provide to shoponn from time to time is and shall be authentic, correct, current and updated and you have all the rights, permissions and consents as may be required to provide such Information to shoponn. 
  * Your providing the Information to shoponn and shoponn’s consequent storage, collection, usage, transfer, access or processing of the same shall not be in violation of any third party agreement, laws, charter documents, judgments, orders and decrees. 

shoponn and each of shoponn entities officers, directors, contractors or agents shall not be responsible for the authenticity of the Information that you or any other user provide to shoponn. You shall indemnify and hold harmless shoponn and each of shoponn entities officers, directors, contracts or agents and any third party relying on the Information provided by you in the event you are in breach of this Privacy Policy including this provision and the immediately preceding provision above. 

Your Information will primarily be stored in electronic form however certain data can also be stored in physical form. We may store, collect, process and use your data in countries other than Republic of India but under compliance with applicable laws. We may enter into agreements with third parties (in or outside of India) to store or process your information or data. These third parties may have their own security standards to safeguard your information or data and we will on commercial reasonable basis require from such third parties to adopt reasonable security standards to safeguard your information / data.

####  E.Sharing of personal information

We may share personal information with our other corporate entities and affiliates. These entities and affiliates may market to you as a result of such sharing unless you explicitly opt-out. We may disclose personal information to third parties. This disclosure may be required for us to provide you access to our Services, to comply with our legal obligations, to enforce our User Agreement, to facilitate our marketing and advertising activities, or to prevent, detect, mitigate, and investigate fraudulent or illegal activities related to our Services. We do not disclose your personal information to third parties for their marketing and advertising purposes without your explicit consent. 

We may disclose personal information if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such disclosure is reasonably necessary to respond to subpoenas, court orders, or other legal process. We may disclose personal information to law enforcement offices, third party rights owners, or others in the good faith belief that such disclosure is reasonably necessary to: enforce our Terms or Privacy Policy; respond to claims that an advertisement, posting or other content violates the rights of a third party; or protect the rights, property or personal safety of our users or the general public. 

We and our affiliates will share / sell some or all of your personal information with another business entity should we (or our assets) plan to merge with, or be acquired by that business entity, or re-organization, amalgamation, restructuring of business. Should such a transaction occur that other business entity (or the new combined entity) will be required to follow this privacy policy with respect to your personal information. 

The Services are not available to, You hereby unconditionally agree and permit that shoponn may transfer, share, disclose or part with all or any of Your Information, within and outside of the Republic of India to various shoponn entities and to third party service providers / partners / banks and financial institutions for one or more of the Purposes or as may be required by applicable law. In such case we will contractually oblige the receiving parties of the Information to ensure the same level of data protection that is adhered to by shoponn under applicable law. 

You acknowledge and agree that, to the extent permissible under applicable laws, it is adequate that when shoponn transfers Your Information to any other entity within or outside your country of residence, shoponn will place contractual obligations on the transferee which will oblige the transferee to adhere to the provisions of this Privacy Policy. 

shoponn may share statistical data and other details (other than Your Personal Information) without your express or implied consent to facilitates various programmes or initiatives launched by shoponn, its affiliates, agents, third party service providers, partners or banks & financial institutions, from time to time. We may transfer/disclose/share Information (other than Your Personal Information) to those parties who support our business, such as providing technical infrastructure services, analyzing how our services are used, measuring the effectiveness of advertisements, providing customer / buyer services, facilitating payments, or conducting academic research and surveys. These affiliates and third party service providers shall adhere to confidentiality obligations consistent with this Privacy Policy.Notwithstanding the above, We use other third parties such as a credit/debit card processing company, payment gateway, pre-paid cards etc. To enable You to make payments for buying products or availing services on shoponn. When You sign up for these services, You may have the ability to save Your card details for future reference and faster future payments. In such case, We may share Your relevant Personal Information as necessary for the third parties to provide such services, including your name, residence and email address. The processing of payments or authorization is solely in accordance with these third parties policies, terms and conditions and we are not in any manner responsible or liable to You or any third party for any delay or failure at their end in processing the payments. 

shoponn may also share Personal Information if shoponn believe it is necessary in order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, violations of various terms and conditions or our policies. 

We reserve the right to disclose your information when required to do so by law or regulation, or under any legal obligation or order under law or in response to a request from a law enforcement or governmental agency or judicial, quasi-judicial or any other statutory or constitutional authority or to establish or exercise our legal rights or defend against legal claims. 

You further agree that such disclosure, sharing and transfer of Your Personal Information and Non-Personal Information shall not cause any wrongful loss to you or to any third party, or any wrongful gain to us or to any third party. 

####  F.Links to Other Sites

Our Website links to other websites that may collect personally identifiable information about you. shoponn.in is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of those linked websites.

Links to third-party advertisements, third-party websites or any third party electronic communication service may be provided on the Website which are operated by third parties and are not controlled by, or affiliated to, or associated with, shoponn unless expressly specified on the Website.

shoponn is not responsible for any form of transmission, whatsoever, received by You from any third party website. Accordingly, shoponn does not make any representations concerning the privacy practices or policies of such third parties or terms of use of such third party websites, nor does shoponn control or guarantee the accuracy, integrity, or quality of the information, data, text, software, music, sound, photographs, graphics, videos, messages or other materials available on such third party websites. The inclusion or exclusion does not imply any endorsement by shoponn of the third party websites, the website’s provider, or the information on the website. The information provided by you to such third party websites shall be governed in accordance with the privacy policies of such third party websites and it is recommended that you review the privacy policy of such third party websites prior to using such websites. 

####  G.Security Precautions

Our Website has stringent security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse, and alteration of the information under our control. Whenever you change or access your account information, we offer the use of a secure server. Once your information is in our possession we adhere to strict security guidelines, protecting it against unauthorized access. 

The security of your Personal Information is important to us. shoponn strives to ensure the security of Your Personal Information and to protect Your Personal Information against unauthorized access or unauthorized alteration, disclosure or destruction. For this purpose, shoponn adopts internal reviews of the data collection, storage and processing practices and security measures, including appropriate encryption and physical security measures to guard against unauthorized access to systems where shoponn stores Your Personal Information. Each of the shoponn entity shall adopt reasonable security practices and procedures as mandated under applicable laws for the protection of Your Information. Provided that your right to claim damages shall be limited to the right to claim only statutory damages under Information Technology Act, 2000 and You hereby waive and release all shoponn entities from any claim of damages under contract or under tort.

If you choose a payment gateway to complete any transaction on Website then Your credit card data may be stored in compliance with industry standards/ recommended data security standard for security of financial information such as the Payment Card Industry Data Security Standard (PCI-DSS). 

shoponn may share your Information with third parties under a confidentiality agreement which inter alia provides for that such third parties not disclosing the Information further unless such disclosure is for the Purpose. However, shoponn is not responsible for any breach of security or for any actions of any third parties that receive your Personal Information. shoponn is not liable for any loss or injury caused to you as a result of you providing your Personal Information to third party (including any third party websites, even if links to such third party websites are provided on the Website). 

Notwithstanding anything contained in this Policy or elsewhere, shoponn shall not be held responsible for any loss, damage or misuse of Your Personal Information, if such loss, damage or misuse is attributable to a Force Majeure Event (as defined below). 

A **"Force Majeure Event"** shall mean any event that is beyond the reasonable control of shoponn and shall include, without limitation, sabotage, fire, flood, explosion, acts of God, civil commotion, strikes or industrial action of any kind, riots, insurrection, war, acts of government, computer hacking, unauthorized access to computer, computer system or computer network,, computer crashes, breach of security and encryption (provided beyond reasonable control of shoponn), power or electricity failure or unavailability of adequate power or electricity. 

While We will endeavor to take all reasonable and appropriate steps to keep secure any Personal Information which We hold about You and prevent unauthorized access, You acknowledge that the internet or computer networks are not fully secure and that We cannot provide any absolute assurance regarding the security of Your Personal Information. 

You agree that all Personal Information shall be retained till such time required for the Purpose or required under applicable law, whichever is later. Non-Personal Information will be retained indefinitely. 

####  H.Choice/Opt-Out 

You agree and acknowledge that you are providing your Information out of your free will. You have an option not to provide or permit shoponn to collect Your Personal Information or later on withdraw Your consent with respect to such Personal Information so provided herein by sending an email to the grievance officer or such other electronic address of the respective shoponn entity as may be notified to You. In such case, you should neither visit any Website nor use any services provided by shoponn entities nor shall contact any of shoponn entities. Further, shoponn may not deliver products to you, upon your order, or shoponn may deny you access from using certain services offered on the Website. 

You can add or update your Personal Information on regular basis. Kindly note that shoponn would retain your previous Personal Information in its records. 

We provide all users with the opportunity to opt-out of receiving non-essential (promotional, marketing-related) communications from us on behalf of our partners, and from us in general, after setting up an account.

If you want to remove your contact information from all shoponn.in lists and newsletters, please email to unsubscribe@shoponn.in 

####  I.Advertisements on shoponn.in 

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. 

####  J.Your Consent

By using the Website and/ or by providing your information, you consent to the collection and use of the information you disclose on the Website in accordance with this Privacy Policy, including but not limited to your consent for sharing your information as per this privacy policy.

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page so that you are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances we disclose it.

####  K.Grievance Officer 

If you find any discrepancies or have any grievances in relation to the collection, storage, use, disclosure and transfer of Your Personal Information under this Privacy Policy or any terms of shoponn’s Terms of Use, Term of Sale and other terms and conditions or polices of any shoponn entity, please contact the following:

In accordance with Information Technology Act 2000 and rules made there under, the name and contact details of the Grievance Officer are provided below: 

Nipurn Engineering Private Limited, C-22., M.I.D.C, Shiroli (pulachi), Kolhapur- 416122.Maharashtra, India

**Email:** grievance.officer@shoponn.in

**Time:** Mon – Sat (9:00 AM – 6:00 PM)

The details of the grievance officer may be changed by us from time to time by updating this Privacy Policy. 

####  L. Business/Asset Sale or Transfer 

shoponn may sell, transfer or otherwise share some or all of its assets, including Your Information in connection with a merger, acquisition, reorganization or sale of assets or business or in the event of bankruptcy. Should such a sale or transfer occur, such shoponn entity will reasonably ensure that the Information you have provided and which we have collected is stored and used by the transferee in a manner that is consistent with this Privacy Policy. Any third party to which any of shoponn entity transfers or sells as aforesaid will have the right to continue to use the Information that you provide to us or collected by us immediately prior to such transfer or sale.

You are also under an obligation to use this Website for reasonable and lawful purposes only, and shall not indulge in any activity that is not envisaged through the Website.

####  M. Further acknowledgements 

Are clear and easily accessible and provide statements of shoponn policies and practices with respective to the Information;The trademarks, logos and service marks displayed on the Website **("Marks")** are the property of shoponn or their vendors or respective third parties. You are not permitted to use the Marks without the prior consent of shoponn, the vendor or the third party that may own the Marks., provides for the various types of personal or sensitive personal data of information to be collected; provides for the purposes of collection and usage of the Information; provides for disclosure of Information; andprovides for reasonable security practices and procedures.
